Amadou KOUYATE

Back-End developer (Laravel)



Personal details



Amadou KOUYATE



🔽 amadoukouyate990@gmail. com



+905453868309



Ankara Ankara/Turkey



January 1st, 1994



Oumé / Côte d'Ivoire



Homme



Ivoirienne



Célibataire



linkedin.com/in/ amadou-kouyate-990

Skills

DUD Laraval

FIIF Lalavei	
JavaScript	••••
Ajax	••••
Bootstrap	••••
Linux	••••
Vue JS and Angular	••••

Profile

Web developer for more than three years, I now want put my skills and my experience at the service of your company to analyze, program and monitor development systems to maintain the satisfaction of customers and employees. To which can be added my excellent adaptability and Communication.

Employment

Back-end Developer

Jun 2021 - Present

Etsetra Analytics, Ankara / Turkey

Management of multiple websites with a single back-office Technology used: Laravel 8, Redis, MySQL, internal APIs

PHP web Developer

May 2020 - May 2021

Freelance, Ankara / Turkey

Realization of the Backend to an health web platform (project duration 5 months)

Realization of The town hall management software (project duration 3 months)

Realization of a stock and shop management software (project duration 4 months)

Web Developer

May 2019 - Dec 2019

SOCOCI, Abidjan

Realization of an online meat sales website (project duration 2 weeks) Realization of a container tracking software from order to delivery (project duration 1 month)

Installation of systems, software maintenance on company computers (transit, accounting and cash services).

Web Project Manager

Nov 2018 - Mar 2019

Group Smarty, Abidjan

Realization of camputer consumables management software (project duration 1 month)

Realization of the GroupSmarty website (duration of the project 2 weeks)

Realization the web version of the TransXpert software (project duration 2 months).

Web Developer

Dec 2016 - Aug 2018

FUTURAMA, Abidjan

Participate in the creation of software for connecting patients, doctors and health centers (project duration 7 months)

Participate in the creation of stock management software for shops, supermarket, garage, etc. (project duration 6 months)

Assistant to the technical manager for 2 months

Redis

Languages

English •••••
French

Turkish

Hobbies

Sport

Cinema

Extracurricular activities

Deputy Secretary of the Fraternal Youth Union of Oumé

Fraternal Youth Union of Oumé, Abidjan

Responsible for scheduling meetings and taking minutes. Administrator of the various accounts of the association on social networks (WhatsApp, Facebook)

Education

Bachelor of Science : Computer

Nov 2017 - Dec 2018

Sep 2017 - Present

Engineering

LEGACY INSTITUTE, Abidjan

Merise and UML Data analysis

Programming with languages such as PHP (PDO)

Expression technique in French and English

Mathematics

BTEC Higher National Diploma or 12th Dec 2014 - Jul 2016 Grade in IT Application Developer

Practical School of the Ivory Coast Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Abidjan

Merise Data analysis,

Programming with languages such as PHP, Visual Basic, C and html Expression technique in French and English

IT negotiation, Mathematics

High-School Diploma

Sep 2011 - Jul 2014

Lycee Moderne Oumé, Oumé

Mathematics and physical sciol

Mathematics and physical sciences

References

Kouakou Wilfried Kouakou

Entrepreneur and web developer (PHP, Android, React, ReactNative), Abidjan

+225 07 08 54 98 33

Alfred Echimane KOUANSAN

Senior Data Warehouse Analyst at Ivorian company Electricity, Abidjan +225 07 48 36 56 90

Stéphane Irié

Senior Consultant at GREEN SERVICES, Abidjan

+225 07 79 50 57 42